islcollective.com 2014-06-26

# 50 000+ Free ESL, EFL worksheets made by teachers for teachers

iSLCollective Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us, as it is to you. This Privacy Policy explains how we acquire personal information through your use of the iSLCollective website and how we will treat such information. We will never sell or rent your personal information to any third party at any time, for any reason.

Information We Gather

When you register with us, we ask you to provide your user name, email address, an account password and your nationality. We may use your email address to send administrative email messages to you from time to time. For certain premium services in the future, we may also request credit card or other payment account information. We may gather other limited information about you, including information about your viewing history, the Internet Protocol address of your originating Internet Service Provider and the type of browser you are using.

How We Use Your Information

We use your information to deliver the services offered by the iSLCollective website; to respond to and process your requests for services and information; to notify you of updated or changed information, promotional opportunities, website features, or services that we offer. We will not send you newsletters or any advertising, except if you have explicitly consented to allow such communications (by "opting-in"). At the same time, we reserve the right to send you notices necessary to maintain your account with iSLCollective.

We will not sell or rent such information of yours to any third party. We handle your sensitive personal information confidentially. We will only disclose your sensitive personal information to a third party if obligated by law to do so. Unless we are prohibited by law from doing so, we will make a reasonable effort to inform you of any such disclosure prior to disclosure.

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who have registered with us, the volume and pattern of traffic to and within the site, etc., to promote the delivery of targeted messages or advertisements to the iSLCollective website while our users are interacting with the iSLCollective site. That information will not identify you, as an individual, in any way.

Technical Tools We Use

A "cookie" (also "tracking cookie," "browser cookie," and "HTTP cookie") is a small piece of text stored on a user's computer by a web browser that assign a unique identifier to your computer so that iSLCollective can "recognize" your computer each time you use it to return to the iSLCollective website. You can also set your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but you should be aware that disabling cookies may limit the scope of service that we are able to provide for you.

Your iSLCollective Password

Your iSLCollective password is unique to your iSLCollective account and serves the purpose of protecting your account from unauthorized access and use. iSLCollective may not be held responsible for any stolen, lost or otherwise disclosed passwords. You are advised to keep away your password from others and should not disclose it to anyone.

Outbound Links to Third Party Websites

The iSLCollective website may contain outbound links to third party websites iSLCollective is not affiliated with. We do not exercise control over any site that may be linked to from content that is displayed within content on this site.You should note that our privacy policy applies only to the iSLCollective site and we do not exercise control over any site that may be linked to from content that is displayed within content on this site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these third party websites. Should you visit such third party websites, you are advised to read their respective privacy policies.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time in our sole discretion. We will not diminish your rights under this policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most changes to be minor. Should we affect a significant change to our policy, we will notify you of those changes through a notice posted on this page when you log in to your iSLCollective account. If we become involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Your Questions about our Privacy Policy

Should you have further questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at support [a.t] islcollective [d.ó.t] com
